<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MeditationApp</string>
    <string name="meditation_time_label">Time: %s</string>
    <string name="guide_initial_prompt">Offer yourself a warm greeting as you settle in.</string>
    <string name="guide_on_start">Take this moment to pause from the busyness of life and simply be here.</string>
    <string name="guide_on_finish">Reflect on the stillness you cultivated. Carry this sense of calm into the rest of your day.</string>
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="language_prompt">Language</string>
    <string-array name="language_options">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>한국어</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="language_codes">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>ko</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="meditation_finished_toast">Meditation finished.</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_0_3_min">0-3 min: Sit or lie down comfortably with a gentle upright posture. Close your eyes or soften your gaze, noticing that you are here in this moment.</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_3_7_min">3-7 min: Bring awareness to the sensations in your body. Slowly scan from head to toe, observing any tension or warmth without judgment.</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_7_12_min">7-12 min: Observe the natural rhythm of your breathing. Feel each inhalation and exhalation. If the mind wanders, kindly return to the breath.</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_12_17_min">12-17 min: Notice any emotions or thoughts that arise. Recognize them without trying to push them away, letting them drift like clouds.</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_17_23_min">17-23 min: Offer yourself gentle words: 'I am doing my best. I am okay in this moment.' Extend silent well-wishes to others: 'May you be peaceful.'</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_23_27_min">23-27 min: Bring your attention back to the physical sensations of your body. Feel your contact with the floor or chair and gently awaken your hands and shoulders.</string>
    <string name="guide_kor_27_30_min">27-30 min: Slowly open your eyes and complete the practice with gratitude. Remember you can return to this calm whenever you wish.</string>
</resources>
